<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>

    <string name="balinese">The breed arose due to a spontaneous genetic mutation in a purebred Siamese that caused the cats to develop a longer coat type. The Balinese cat does not have any links with Indonesia (Siamese cats are from Thailand). Breeders created the Balinese name since they thought the cat\'s grace and elegance mirrored that of the temple dancers of Bali.</string>
    <string name="bengal">Although Bengal cats are technically considered modern-day cats, their origins are linked to Asia. Bengals result from breeding an Asian leopard cat (Felis bengalensis) with domestic cats like Abyssinians, Egyptian maus, or American shorthairs. Created by Jean Sudgen Mills in the 1970s, she bred Bengals to have the personality of a house cat but the exotic look of a wild, big cat.</string>
    <string name="birman">The Birman breed likely came into existence after being transported from Burma (now Myanmar) to France. People bred that Burma-native cat with other cats in France, often Siamese. The Birman is a chatty cat (like Siamese) with a softer voice that frequently chirps and converses with his people. The Birman’s long coat is single-length with no undercoat.</string>
    <string name="burmese">Originated in Burma—presently known as Myanmar—Burmese cats were held sacred in temples and monasteries around the country. One cat, however, is considered the "founding mother" of the breed: A cat named Wong Mau was transported from Burma to the United States by a sailor in the 1930s and given to Dr. Joseph G. Thompson in San Francisco. There, Dr. Thompson started a breeding program crossbreeding Wong Mau with a Siamese to establish the Burmese breed further.</string>
    <string name="dragonli">Called "li hua mao," which translates to "fox flower cat" in Chinese, the dragon li is thought to be a naturally occurring breed that existed in the wild for centuries. Many believe that the dragon li first originated from the Chinese mountain cat and domesticated itself over time. The dragon li is unofficially considered the national cat of China and is rarely seen outside its origin country.</string>
    <string name="himalayan">The Himalayan breed is a hybrid of Persian and Siamese cats. The result is a beautiful feline with a long, silky, Persian-like coat and Siamese-like pointed coloring and bright blue eyes. This breed is stockier, thicker-bodied; it is considered the "gentle giant" of the feline world. </string>
    <string name="japanesebobtail">The Japanese bobtail\'s shortened tail—often referred to as a "pom"—is the breed\'s most distinguishing characteristic. The result of a naturally occurring genetic mutation, the shortened tail can be straight, bent, or kinked. In addition to their unique appearance, Japanese bobtails have a fascinating history, which many believe stretches back to China or Korea over 1,000 years ago.</string>
    <string name="korat">Considered one of the rarest cat breeds, the Korat originated in Thailand centuries ago. Ancient artifacts dating back to the 13th century show the first references of Korats. This cat was brought to Europe in the 1800s, where they became known as "blue Siamese" for their blue coats and Siamese-like appearance.</string>
    <string name="orientalshorthair">The Oriental shorthair is considered an offshoot of the Siamese cat family, including the Balinese and Oriental longhair. During World War II, domestic cat populations were, sadly, dwindling. Siamese cat breeds began introducing other domestic breeds like Russian blues and Abyssinians into their lines to revive these populations. The result was kittens with tri-color points like a Siamese with coats that came in a wide variety of unique colors.</string>
    <string name="persian">Persian cats are probably best-known for glamorous looks and long, silky fur. Their beauty—along with their sweet, calm demeanors—have made them one of the most popular cat breeds in the United States. Their background is a little unclear, but it\'s commonly believed that Persians originated in Persia (modern-day Iran) or Turkey sometime during the 1600s and moved into Europe.</string>
    <string name="siamese">Best-known for their striking, tri-color coats and bright, blue eyes, Siamese cats are one of the world\'s most popular cat breeds today. They also one of the oldest breeds to originate in Asia. They hail from Thailand—formerly known as Siam. Siamese cats were once considered royalty and could only be owned by kings and other royal family members.</string>
    <string name="singapura">Known as the smallest domestic cat breed, the Singapura, or Pura, shines with its unique looks and loving personality. This breed only weighs 4 to 8 pounds when fully grown and sports large, round eyes, big ears, and a sepia-colored coat. Once a common street cat in Singapore, these purebred felines are now prized pets.</string>
    <string name="thai">The Thai is a medium sized cat, robust and cobby in build, but never large or coarse. Alert and attractive, they have a heart shaped face with large, mobile ears. The Thai cat is a shorthaired cat breed that has a flat, short coat that is really soft in texture. </string>
    <string name="tonkinese">A Tonkinese is a Siamese and Burmese cat lover\'s dream. It is the product when the two breeds are mixed. It exhibits the best of both breeds: It\'s smart, sweet, and social. The cat is a beautiful pointed cat with soft, diluted colors and a stunningly unique personality. </string>
    <string name="turkishangora">The Turkish Angora is a naturally occurring breed believed to have originated in Turkey during the 15th century. Some origin theories say that the Turkish Angora results from a genetic mutation in an African wildcat. Conversely, others believe the cats developed their long, silky coats to protect them from harsh, snowy climates in Ankara (formerly Angora).</string>
</resources>